http://www.draftexpress.com/privacy-policy

Privacy Policy
This privacy policy has been compiled to better serve those who are concerned with how their 'Personally Identifiable Information' (PII) is being used online. PII, as described in US privacy law and information security, is information that can be used on its own or with other information to identify, contact, or locate a single person, or to identify an individual in context. Please read our privacy policy carefully to get a clear understanding of how we collect, use, protect or otherwise handle your Personally Identifiable Information in accordance with our website.
What personal information do we collect from the people that visit our blog, website or app?
We receive information about you from various sources, including through your use of the website and from various third party websites and other services. When you use the website, you are consenting to the collection, transfer, manipulation, storage, disclosure and other uses of your information as described in this Privacy Policy.
The information we gather from users enables us to personalize and improve our website. We collect the following types of information from our users.
Personal Information Collected Automatically:
We receive and store certain types of information whenever you interact with our website. We automatically receive and record information on our server logs from your browser including your IP address, cookie information, and the page you requested. If you access the website through an Application, we may also collect your location information if you have selected settings that enable us to collect such information.
Generally, our website automatically collects usage information, such as the numbers and frequency of visitors to our Site and its components, similar to TV ratings that indicate how many people watched a particular show. We may use this data in aggregate form, that is, as a statistical measure, but not in a manner that would identify you personally. This type of aggregate data enables us to figure out how often users use parts of the website so that we can improve and make the website appealing to as many users as possible, and improve. As part of this use of information, we may provide aggregate information to our partners about how our users, collectively, use the Site and Application. We share this type of statistical data so that our partners also understand how often people use their services and our Service, so that they, too, may provide you with an optimal online experience.
Sign-In Information Collected:
By creating an account or by signing in for the website using a Third Party Service (as discussed below), you may provide us certain Personal Information, and you may allow others, including us, to identify you. We may use your contact information to send you information about our website. You may unsubscribe from certain of these messages through instructions in the emails we send you, but certain communications, such as important information regarding the website are not subject to unsubscription.
Financial Information:
We do not currently collect financial information, such as your payment method (valid credit card number, type, expiration date or other financial information); that information is collected and stored by our third party payment processing company (the"Payment Processor"), and use and storage of that information is governed by the Payment Processor’s applicable terms of service and privacy policy.
Third Party Services:
As mentioned above, we may allow you to link your accounts to Third Party Services, such as Facebook, Google+ and Twitter ("Third Party Accounts") to the website. If you elect to link to such Third Party Services, we may collect information related to your use of that Third Party Service, such as access tokens made available by that Third Party Service, and other content or information that is provided to us from that Third Party Service. For example, we may receive additional information about you through that Third Party Service, such as gender, age, education, occupation, hobbies, interests, relationship status, and zip code. Third Party Services may also have the ability to restrict the information that is provided to us. Moreover, we don’t actually store your passwords for those Third Party Accounts. Instead, we just use an authentication token to verify your user name.
Any information that you elect to distribute through any of these Third Party Services by using the website is instantly provided to such Third Party Services and, after leaving our servers, becomes accessible by such Third Party Services. Therefore, in addition to reviewing this Privacy Policy, you should also review the privacy policies and terms of use of the Third Party Services that you access through the Service.
Email Communications:
We may receive email activity data from your personal email provider. We use this data to understand and enhance our email communications and the Services. If you do not want to receive email from us, you can unsubscribe from specific email communications or all email communications from us by clicking the "unsubscribe" link in any email we send to you. Please note that certain communications, such as important information regarding the Service are not subject to unsubscription.
Cookies:
Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that we transfer to your computer’s hard drive through your browser to enable our systems to recognize your browser and tell us how and when pages in our Site are visited and by how many people. Our cookies do not collect Personal Information, and we do not combine the general information collected through cookies with other Personal Information to tell us who you are or what your email address is.
Most browsers have an option for turning off the cookie feature, which will prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, as well as (depending on the sophistication of your browser software) allowing you to decide on acceptance of each new cookie in a variety of ways.
Third Party Cookies and Web Beacons:
We and our authorized third party partners may use device identification, cookies, web beacons, or similar technologies to deliver more relevant advertising and communications to consumers. This advertising is sometimes called interest-based or online behavioral advertising. Such advertisements are generally targeted and served to particular users (as described in more detail below) and may come from third party companies called "ad networks". Ad networks include third party ad servers, ad agencies, ad technology vendors and research firms. We do not provide Personal Information to any ad networks for use outside of the Services.
Interest-based advertisements may be targeted to users who fit a certain general profile category, may be based on anonymized information inferred from information provided to us by a user (including Personal Information such as gender or age), may be based on usage patterns of particular users on the website, or may be based on your activity on Third Party Services. Ad networks may set cookies through our Site that enable them to retarget you on other sites.
If you would like an ad network to not set or use cookies on your computer or mobile device, you can visit the following site http://www.aboutads.info/choices/.
How do we use your information?
Internal Use: We use Personal Information to deliver certain aspects of the Service to you, to contact you when necessary, to respond to your inquiries for additional information, to provide you with additional information according to your preferences, and for our other business purposes. Sometimes Personal Information may be used to send you information about services, and forums that are available at the Site or other websites. At your election at any time ("opt-out"), you may choose to stop receiving future communications from us by clicking the "unsubscribe" link in an email we send you.
Third Party Services: As discussed above, the Service allows you to connect with certain Third Party Services. When you broadcast information to such Third Party Services, such information is no longer under our control and is subject to the terms of use and privacy policies of such third parties.
How do we protect your information?
We do not use vulnerability scanning and/or scanning to PCI standards.
We only provide articles and information. We never ask for credit card numbers, that information is collected and stored by our third party payment processing company (the"Payment Processor"), and use and storage of that information is governed by the Payment Processor’s applicable terms of service and privacy policy.
We do not use Malware Scanning.
We do not use an SSL certificate.
We take appropriate security measures (including physical, electronic and procedural measures) to help safeguard your Personal Information from unauthorized access and disclosure. For example, only authorized employees and third parties who have agreed to be bound by confidentiality restrictions, such as consultants, may be permitted to access Personal Information, and they may do so only for permitted business purposes. In addition, we use SSL encryption in the transmission of your sensitive Personal Information between your system and ours, and we use firewalls to help prevent unauthorized persons from gaining access to your Personal Information.
If you access a Third Party Service via the Service, you may have additional or different sign-on protections via that Third Party Service. We are not responsible for the privacy policies and/or practices on other websites. When linking to another website, you should read the privacy policy stated on that website.
We want you to feel confident using the Service and endeavor to protect your Personal Information we hold in our records. However, no system can be completely secure. Unauthorized entry or use, hardware or software failure, and other factors, may compromise the security of user information at any time. Therefore, although we take steps to secure your information, we do not promise, and you should not expect, that your Personal Information will always remain secure. Users should also take care with how they handle and disclose their Personal Information and should avoid sending Personal Information through insecure e-mail.
We only provide articles and information. We never ask for personal or private information like names, email addresses, or credit card numbers.
Do we use 'cookies'?
Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the site's or service provider's systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. For instance, we use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart. They are also used to help us understand your preferences based on previous or current site activity, which enables us to provide you with improved services. We also use cookies to help us compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future.
We use cookies to:
Keep track of advertisements.
Compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interactions in order to offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may also use trusted third-party services that track this information on our behalf.
You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your browser settings. Since browser is a little different, look at your browser's Help Menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies.
If you turn cookies off, some features will be disabled. It won't affect the user's experience that make your site experience more efficient and may not function properly.
However, you will still be able to place orders.
Third-party disclosure
We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your Personally Identifiable Information.
Third-party links
We do not include or offer third-party products or services on our website.
Google
Google's advertising requirements can be summed up by Google's Advertising Principles. They are put in place to provide a positive experience for users. here
We use Google AdSense Advertising on our website.
Google, as a third-party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on previous visits to our site and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt-out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google Ad and Content Network privacy policy.
We have implemented the following:
Demographics and Interests Reporting
We, along with third-party vendors such as Google use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookies) and third-party cookies (such as the DoubleClick cookie) or other third-party identifiers together to compile data regarding user interactions with ad impressions and other ad service functions as they relate to our website.
Opting out:
Users can set preferences for how Google advertises to you using the Google Ad Settings page. Alternatively, you can opt out by visiting the Network Advertising Initiative Opt Out page or by using the Google Analytics Opt Out Browser add on.
California Online Privacy Protection Act
CalOPPA is the first state law in the nation to require commercial websites and online services to post a privacy policy. The law's reach stretches well beyond California to require any person or company in the United States (and conceivably the world) that operates websites collecting Personally Identifiable Information from California consumers to post a conspicuous privacy policy on its website stating exactly the information being collected and those individuals or companies with whom it is being shared. - See more at: http://consumercal.org/california-online-privacy-protection-act-caloppa/#sthash.0FdRbT51.dpuf
According to CalOPPA, we agree to the following:
Users can visit our site anonymously.
Once this privacy policy is created, we will add a link to it on our home page or as a minimum, on the first significant page after entering our website.
Our Privacy Policy link includes the word 'Privacy' and can be easily be found on the page specified above.
You will be notified of any Privacy Policy changes:
On our Privacy Policy Page
Can change your personal information:
By logging in to your account (if applicable)
How does our site handle Do Not Track signals?
We honor Do Not Track signals and Do Not Track, plant cookies, or use advertising when a Do Not Track (DNT) browser mechanism is in place.
Does our site allow third-party behavioral tracking?
It's also important to note that we do not allow third-party behavioral tracking
COPPA (Children Online Privacy Protection Act)
When it comes to the collection of personal information from children under the age of 13 years old, the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA) puts parents in control. The Federal Trade Commission, United States' consumer protection agency, enforces the COPPA Rule, which spells out what operators of websites and online services must do to protect children's privacy and safety online.
We do not specifically market to children under the age of 13 years old.
Fair Information Practices
The Fair Information Practices Principles form the backbone of privacy law in the United States and the concepts they include have played a significant role in the development of data protection laws around the globe. Understanding the Fair Information Practice Principles and how they should be implemented is critical to comply with the various privacy laws that protect personal information.
In order to be in line with Fair Information Practices we will take the following responsive action, should a data breach occur:
Within 7 business days
We will notify the users via in-site notification
Within 7 business days
We also agree to the Individual Redress Principle which requires that individuals have the right to legally pursue enforceable rights against data collectors and processors who fail to adhere to the law. This principle requires not only that individuals have enforceable rights against data users, but also that individuals have recourse to courts or government agencies to investigate and/or prosecute non-compliance by data processors.
CAN SPAM Act
The CAN-SPAM Act is a law that sets the rules for commercial email, establishes requirements for commercial messages, gives recipients the right to have emails stopped from being sent to them, and spells out tough penalties for violations.
We collect your email address in order to:
Send information, respond to inquiries, and/or other requests or questions
Process orders and to send information and updates pertaining to orders.
Send you additional information related to your product and/or service
To be in accordance with CANSPAM, we agree to the following:
Not use false or misleading subjects or email addresses.
Identify the message as an advertisement in some reasonable way.
Include the physical address of our business or site headquarters.
Monitor third-party email marketing services for compliance, if one is used.
Honor opt-out/unsubscribe requests quickly.
Allow users to unsubscribe by using the link at the bottom of each email.
If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, you can email us at
Follow the instructions at the bottom of each email.
and we will promptly remove you from ALL correspondence.
Contacting Us
If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy, you may contact us using the information below.
support__at__draftexpress__dot__com
© 2020 DraftExpress LLC All rights reserved.
